https://unitedpkg.com/privacy-policy/

Privacy Policy
Learn how we keep your privacy safe while using our site.
Privacy Policy
Your privacy is critically important to us. These privacy policies outline the rules and regulations for the use of United Packaging Website.
United Packaging is located at:
102 Wharton Road
Bristol, PA 19007
United States
It is United Packaging’s policy to respect your privacy regarding any information we may collect while operating our Website. This Privacy Policy applies to www.unitedpkg.com (hereinafter, “us”, “we”, or “www.unitedpkg.com“). We respect your privacy and are committed to protecting personally-identifiable information you may provide us through the Website. We have adopted this privacy policy (“Privacy Policy”) to explain what information may be collected on our Website, how we use this information, and under what circumstances we may disclose the information to third parties. This Privacy Policy applies only to information we collect through the Website and does not apply to our collection of information from other sources collected on our Website, how we use this information, and under what circumstances we may disclose the information to third parties. This Privacy Policy applies only to information we collect through the Website and does not apply to our collection of information from other sources.
This Privacy Policy, together with the Terms and Conditions posted on our Website, set forth the general rules and policies governing your use of our Website. Depending on your activities when visiting our Website, you may be required to agree to additional terms and conditions.
Website Visitors
Like most Website operators, United Packaging collects non-personally-identifying information of the sort that web browsers and servers typically make available, such as the browser type, language preference, referring site, and the date and time of each visitor request. United Packaging’s purpose in collecting non-personally-identifying information is to better understand how United Packaging’s visitors use its Website. From time to time, United Packaging may release non-personally-identifying information in the aggregate, e.g., by publishing a report on trends in the usage of its Website.
United Packaging also collects potentially personally-identifying information like Internet Protocol (IP) addresses for logged in users and for users leaving comments on www.unitedpkg.com blog posts. United Packaging only discloses logged in user and commenter IP addresses under the same circumstances that it uses and discloses personally-identifying information as described herein.
Gathering of Personally-Identifying Information
Certain visitors to United Packaging’s Websites choose to interact with United Packaging in ways that require United Packaging to gather personally-identifying information. The amount and type of information that United Packaging gathers depends on the nature of the interaction. For example, we ask visitors who sign up for a blog at www.unitedpkg.com to provide a username and email address. Any personally-identifying information that is gathered is used for internal purposes only to provide more relevant and personalized communications from United Packaging. We do not sell any personally-identifying information to 3rd parties.
Security
The security of your Personal Information is important to us, but remember that no method of transmission over the Internet, or method of electronic storage is 100% secure. While we strive to use commercially acceptable means to protect your Personal Information, we cannot guarantee its absolute security.
Advertisements
Ads appearing on our Website may be delivered to users by advertising partners, who may set cookies. These cookies allow the ad server to recognize your computer each time they send you an online advertisement to compile information about you or others who use your computer. This information allows ad networks to, among other things, deliver targeted advertisements that they believe will be of most interest to you. This Privacy Policy covers the use of cookies by United Packaging and does not cover the use of cookies by any advertisers.
Links To External Sites
Our Service may contain links to external sites that are not operated by us. If you click on a third-party link, you will be directed to that third party’s site. We strongly advise you to review the Privacy Policy and terms and conditions of every site you visit.
We have no control over, and assume no responsibility for the content, privacy policies or practices of any third-party sites, products or services.
Aggregated Statistics
United Packaging may collect statistics about the behavior of visitors to its Website. United Packaging may display this information publicly or provide it to others. However, United Packaging does not disclose your personally-identifying information.
Cookies
To enrich and perfect your online experience, United Packaging uses “Cookies”, similar technologies and services provided by others to display personalized content, appropriate advertising and store your preferences on your computer.
A cookie is a string of information that a Website stores on a visitor’s computer, and that the visitor’s browser provides to the Website each time the visitor returns. United Packaging uses cookies to help United Packaging identify and track visitors, their usage of www.unitedpkg.com and their Website access preferences. United Packaging visitors who do not wish to have cookies placed on their computers should set their browsers to refuse cookies before using United Packaging’s Websites, with the drawback that certain features of United Packaging’s Websites may not function properly without the aid of cookies.
By continuing to navigate our Website without changing your cookie settings, you hereby acknowledge and agree to United Packaging’s use of cookies.
E-commerce
Those who engage in transactions with United Packaging – by purchasing United Packaging’s services or products, are asked to provide additional information, including as necessary the personal and financial information required to process those transactions. In each case, United Packaging collects such information only insofar as is necessary or appropriate to fulfill the purpose of the visitor’s interaction with United Packaging. United Packaging does not disclose personally-identifying information other than as described herein. And visitors can always refuse to supply personally-identifying information, with the caveat that it may prevent them from engaging in certain Website-related activities.
Business Transfers
If United Packaging, or substantially all of its assets, were acquired, or in the unlikely event that United Packaging goes out of business or enters bankruptcy, user information would be one of the assets that is transferred or acquired by a third party. You acknowledge that such transfers may occur, and that any acquirer of United Packaging may continue to use your personal information as set forth in this policy.
Privacy Policy Changes
Although most changes are likely to be minor, United Packaging may change its Privacy Policy from time to time, and in United Packaging’s sole discretion. United Packaging encourages visitors to frequently check this page for any changes to its Privacy Policy. Your continued use of this site after any change in this Privacy Policy will constitute your acceptance of such change.
Credit & Contact Information
If you have any questions about this Privacy Policy, please contact us via email or phone.
Let's get acquainted
Getting to know you and your business is the first step. Sign up to talk to an Account Manager today.
Close
